E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
- Publicity files
  - Gibbs - Gissing (Box 39)
    Gibbs, A. Hamilton Items
    Gibbs, Sir Philip Correspondence & Items
    Gilbert, Ariadne (W.H. Hudson)
    Gilbreath
    Gill, Jack
    Gillian, Florence
    Gilman, Lawrence Correspondence
    Gilman, S.C.
    Ginn, Ann
    Gissing, George Correspondence
    Gissing, George
  - Gitlow - Goldie (Box 39)
    Gitlow, Benjamin Correspondence & Items
    Glover, Florida R.
    Goddard, Harold, Proe (W.H.Hudson - Birdman)
    Godwin, A.H.
    Goethe (Everyman's)
    Goldberg, Issac
    Goldberg, Issac 1919-1920
    Goldie, Valentine
  - Golding - Goldman (Box 40)
    Golding, Louis Correspondence
    Golding, Louis Biog., Photos, & Items
    Goldman, Lawrence
  - Gompers I (Box 40)
    Gompers, Samuel #1 Correspondence w/ Mr. Macrae 1918-1921
  - Gompers II (Box 40)
    Gompers, Samuel Correspondence #2 (1923 - Dec. 11, 1924)
  - Gompers III (Box 40)
    Gompers, Samuel Biog. & Photos
    Gompers, Samuel Correspondence #3 (Dec.13, 1924 - 1928)
  - Gompers IV (Box 40)
    Gompers, Samuel Articles
    Gompers, Samuel Reviews - 1943 - 1 Vol. Ed.
  - Gompers (Box 40)
    Gompers Samuel Reviews - 2 Vol. Ed.
  - Goncharor - Gordon (Box 40)
    Goncharor "Oblomor"
    Goodman, Paul (History of the Jews) Correspondence
    Gordon, Manya (Mrs. Simeon Strusky)
    Gordon, Dorothy
  - Gordon (Box 40)
    Gordon, Dorothy 1928-1932
  - Gordon - Grey (Box 40)
    Gordon, Dorothy 1933-1934
    Gordon. L.L.
    Gordon, Col. R.H.
    Gordon, Samuel
    Gore, John, ed.
    Gorrell. Lord Biog. & Items
    Gosling, Cecil
    Graham, Eleanor Biog. & Items
    Granny's Story Box
    Grant, Mrs. Cyril F.
    Graham, Cyril F.
    Gram, Robert
    Gray, Madeline
  - Green I (Box 40)
    Green, Anne Biog. & Photos
    Green, Anne Correspondence
  - Green II (Box 40)
    Green, Anne Paris Letter to Mr. Macrae
  - Green - Grey (Box 40)
    Green, Anne 1929-1934
    Green, Fitshugh, Lieut. Com. Correspondence
    Green, Henry
    Green, Julien Macrae, John
    Greenlaw, Olga
    Greewalt, Mary
    Gregory, Prof. T.E. Biog. & Items
    Grey, Earl (Fly Fishing) Correspondence
  - Griffith - Guthrie (Box 40)
    Griffith, Linda A. (Mrs. D.W.)
    Griffith, William Biog. & Items
    Griffith, Wyn
    Grilley, Virginia
    Gronowicz, Antoni
    Grzesinski, Albert Biog., Photos & Items
  - Guthrie (Box 40)
    photocopies of various reviews
  - Guiterman (Box 41)
    Guiterman, Aurthur Correspondence
    Guiterman, Aurthur Reviews
    Guiterman, Aurthur
  - Gwatkin - Halkett (Box 41)
    Gwatkin-Williams, R.S.
    Gypsy Rickwood
    Haas, Aurthur
    Hadfield, Miles Biog. & Items
    Haffner, Sebastian
    Haight, Elizabeth
    Haire, Norman
    Haldane, J.B.S. Correspondence
    Haldane, J.B. Items
    Halkett, Sarah Stokes
  - Hall - Hambledon (Box 41)
    Hall, Bertha Parker
    Hall, Fielding
    Hall, H.S.
    Hallack, Cecily
    Hallock, G.T. "The Boy Who Was"
    Halstead, Ivor
    Hamaide, Mlle A.
    Hamblen, Emily S. 1925-1934
    Hambledon, Phyllis
  - Hamilton - Hankey (Box 41)
    Hamilton, Cicly
    Hamilton, Clayton Correspondence
    Hamilton, Clive
    Hamilton, Stevenson
    Hankey, Donald #2 Correspondence
    Hankey, Donlad #1 Correspondence
  - Hanna - Hasbrouck (Box 41)
    Hanna, Evelyn
    Harlow, Alvin F. Correspondence on Eddie Foy
    Harper, Wilhelmina
    Harper, Wilhelmina 1933-1934
    Harr, L.L.
    Harris, H. Wilson
    Harris, John
    Harrow, Benjamin
    Hart, Archibold
    Hartland, E.S.
    Hartman, Gertrude
    Hasbrouck, Muriel
  - Haskell - Hazelett (Box 41)
    Haskell, Helen Correspondence
    Haskell, Helen 1929-1934
    Hatcher, Dr. O. Latham
    Havergal, Frnces
    Hawkins, John & Ward
    Hayes, James M.
    Hazelett, C.E.
  - Hazlitt - Hedin (Box 41)
    Hazlitt, Henry Reviews
    Hearnshaw, F.J.C.
    Heaton, John L. Correspondence
    Heaton, Rose Henniker
    Hecht, George L. Correspondence
    Hecht, Goerge L. Correspondence
    Hedin, Sven Biog, Photos, & Items
  - Hedin I (Box 41)
    Hedin, Sven Reviews
    Hedin, Sven 1932
  - Hedin II (Box 41)
    Hedin, Sven 1933
    Hedin, Alma
    Hedin, Sven Correspondence
    Hedin, Sven Articles and Personal Items
  - Hedin III (Box 41)
    Hedin, Sven 1934
  - Heermance - Herford (Box 41)
    Heermance, Edgar L.
    Hegy, Dr. Reginald
    Heine, Heinrich (12 Volumes)
    Helion, Jean
    Henderson, Daniel Correspondence
    Hennessy, Francis X Correspondence
    Henry, Stuart Reviews
    Henry, Stuart Correspondence
    Hepworth, George
    Herford, Oliver (Mrs.) etc. Correspondence
  - Herold - Hickson (Box 41)
    Herols, Don Correspondence
    Herold, Don Correspondence
    Hervey, Antoinette and Walter L -
    Heydenau, Fredrick
    Hibbert, Eloise Talcott
    Hickson, James Moore
  - Heitt - Hill (Box 41)
    Heitt, Helen
    Hill, Ketherine
    Hill, Mabel
  - Hill - Hogan (Box 42)
    Hill, Patty
    Hine, Reginald L.
    Hinkinson, Pamela
    History of Garden Art Reviews
    Hirschfeld, Albert
    Hoben, Alice M.
    Hodgetts, E. Brayley
    Hoffamm, Melita
    "Prof. Haffmann" Lewis, Angelo
    Hogan, Erlin
  - Hogeboom - Holland (Box 42)
    Hogeboom, Amy
    Hogen, Inez 1932-1938
    Hogner, Dorothy & Nils
    Holding, Elizabeth Sanxay Correspondence
    Holding, Elizabeth Sanxay
    Hole, Dean
    Holland, Clive
    Holland, Marty
  - Holloway - Hopkins (Box 42)
    Holloway, Elizabeth H.
    Holmes, Edmond
    Holt, Winifred (Mrs. Rufus Mather)
    Hooke, Nina Warner
    Hooke, Nina Warner Correspondence
    Hoover, Herbert
    Hopkins, Arthur
    Hopkins, Gerard
  - Hopkins - Houdini (Box 42)
    Horan, Kenneth
    Houdini, Harry Articles & Reviews
    Houdini, Harry Correspondence
    Houdini, Harry Biog., Photos & Items
  - Howard - Hoyt (Box 42)
    Howard, Francis Morton
    Howe, Gertrude
    Howes, Royce
    Hoyer, Niels
    Hoyt, Mrs. John Sherman Correspondence on "Spirit"
    Hoyt, Mrs. John Sherman Correspondence
  - Huddleston - Hudson (Box 42)
    Huddleston, Sisley Correspondence
    Huddleston, Sisley Biog., Photos & Items
    Huddleston, Sisley Reviews
    Hudson, W.H. Reviews
  - Hudson I (Box 42)
  - Hudson II (Box 42)
  - Hudson III (Box 42)
    Hudson, W.H. Articles and Personal Items
  - Hudson IV (Box 42)
    Hudson, W.H. Correspondence
    Hudson, W.H. Items
  - Hudson V (Box 42)
    Hudson, W.H. "Literary Notes"
  - Hudson VI (Box 42)
  - Hudson - Humphrey (Box 42)
    Hudson, W.H. Articles & Special Columns
    Hugel, Baron Von
    Huges, John Scott
    Huie, William B.
    Hull, A. Eaglefield
    Hullinger, Edwin W.
    Humphrey, Lucy H.
  - Humphrey (Box 42)
    Humphrey, Zephine Correspondence
    Humphrey Fahnestock, Zephine 1928-1934
  - Hungerford - Hyslop (Box 43)
    Hungerford, Edward
    Hunt, H.E.
    Hunt, Leigh
    Hunt, Violet
    Huntington, Bishop F.D.
    Huntington, W.R. (Eng.)
    Hurley, Vic
    Hurrell, A.G.
    Hutton, Edward
    Hyslop, James H. Correspondence
  - Ichikawa - Ireland (Box 43)
    Ichikawa, Haruko Biog., Photos & Items
    Imrey, Ferenc and Palen, L.S.
    Incentive Taxation Reviews
    Initiate (The) Reviews
    Inamn, Arthur
    Ireland, Alleyne Revs., Adventure With A Genius
  - Ireland - Irwin (Box 43)
    Ireland, Alleyne
    Ireland, Mary E. (1895)
    Irvine, Alexander
    Irvine, Harry
    Irvine, Laurence
    Irving, R.L.G.
    Irwin, Will #1 Correspondence
  - Irwin - Jacob (Box 43)
    Irwin, Will #2 Correspondence
    Irwin, Will #3 Correspondence
    Irwin, W.W.
    Izzi, Basil
    Jackson, Gabrielle Correspondence
    Jackson, Henry E.
    Jackson, J. Henry
    Jacob, Cary F.
  - Jacobson - Jenningson (Box 43)
    Jacobson, Harold S.
    James, Henry Correspondence
    James, Winnifred (Mrs. DeJan)
    James, Sandra
    James, Winifred
    Jameson, Margaret Storm
    Jarvis, Major C.S.
    Janis, Elise
    Jefferies, Richard Items
    Jefferies, Richard Reviews
    Jeffers, Leory
    Jefferson, Beatrice
    Jenison, Madge Reviews - Sunrise Turn
  - Jenkin - Joad (Box 43)
    Jenkin, A.K. Hamilton
    Jenkins, Herbert
    Jennings, Alice Denton
    Jennings, Hargrave The Rosicrucians
    Jepson, Edgar
    Jessup, Elon
    Joad, C.E.M. Correspondence
    Joad, C.E.M. Prof. Biog., Photos & Items
  - Joad (Box 43)
    Joad, C.E.M. Reviews
  - John - Johns (Box 43)
    John, Evan Biog., Photos & Items
    John, Evan Correspondence
    Johns, Rowland
  - Johnson - Johnston (Box 43)
    Johnson, Mrs. Arthur
    Johnson, Avery F.
    Johnson, Buford V.
    Johnson, Burges Biographical & Items
    Johnson, Burges Correspondence #1
    Johnson, Harriet
    Johnston, J.C. Book of the Beloved
    Johnston, J.C. Book of the Beloved Correspondence
  - Johnston - Jordan (Box 43)
    Johnston, Marian
    Johnston, Mary
    Johnston, Stanley
    Johnstone, G.H. Correspondence on "Prosper Merimae"
    Jones, Charles Reed
    Jones, Daniel
    Jones, F. Elwyn
    Jones, Henry Arthur Correspondence
    Jones, Idwal
    Jones, Robert W.
    Jordan, Kate Correspondence
  - Kaempffert - Karsavina (Box 43)
    Kaempffert, Waldemar
    Kahler, Wood
    Kahn, Eritz
    Kaltenbow, H.V.
    Karsavina Items
    Karsavina Reviews of "Theatre Street"
  - Kaslund - Kaye-Smith (Box 43)
    Kaslund, Henning Correspondence
    Katz, Armand
    Kawakami, K.K.
    Kaye-Smith, Shelia Correspondence #1
    Kaye-Smith, Shelia Biog., Photos & Items
  - Kaye-Smith (Box 43)
    Kaye-Smith, Shelia Correspondence #2
    Kaye-Smith, Shelia Articles & Items
  - Kaye-Smith (Box 44)
    Kaye-Smith, Shelia Reviews
    Kaye-Smith, Shelia Reader's Reports
  - Keable (Box 44)
    Keable, Robert #1 Correspondence (1919-1922)
  - Keable - Keeler (Box 44)
    Keable, Robert #2 Correspondence (1923-1935)
    Keable, Robert Reader's Report
    Keable, Robert Clippings, Comments
    Keeler, Harry Stephen Items
    Keeler, Harry Stephen 1934
  - Keeler I (Box 44)
    Keeler, Harry Stephen 1933
    Keeler, Harry Stephen 1932
  - Keeler II (Box 44)
    Keeler, Harry Stephen 1931
  - Keeler (Box 44)
    Harry Stephen Keeler 1927-1928
  - Keeler - Kelley (Box 44)
    Harry Stephen Keeler Service for Authors
    Kellet, E.E.
    Kelley, Florence Finch Biog., Photos & Items
    Kelley, Florence Finch Correspondence
  - Kelley - Kennedy (Box 44)
    Kelley, Florence Finch Correspondence #2
    Kelley, Florence Finch Reviews
    Kennedy, H.A.
    Kennedy, H.A. 1934
    Kennedy, H.A. 1932-1933
    Kennedy, H.A. 1928-1931
  - Kerlin - Keyser (Box 44)
    Kerlin, Robert Correspondence
    Kern, Corrine Johnson
    Keyes, Lord (Admiral of the Fleet) Obit.
    Keyser, Arthur
  - Keyser - Kinsky (Box 44)
    Keyser, Prof. Cassius J. Correspondence #1
    Keyser, Prof. Cassius J. Correspondence #2
    Keyser, Prof. Cassius J. Correspondence #3 & Items
    Keyser, Prof. Cassius J. Reviews
    Kinsky
  - Kirby - Kopman (Box 44)
    Kirkland, Winifred
    Knight, Marjorie
    Knox, Howard V.
    Knox, Ronald Father Biog.
    Kobbe, Herman
    Koehler (West Point Manual)
    Kopman, Henry Hazlitt
  - Korzybski (Box 45)
    Korzybski, Count Alfred 1921 Correspondence #1
    Korzybski, Count Alfred 1922-30 Correspondence #2
    Korzybski, Count Alfred 1931 Correspondence #3
    Korzybski, Count Alfred Reviews
  - Korzybski - Lawrence (Box 45)
    Korzybski, Count Articles & Items
    Kramer, Anne
    Kraus, Rene
    Kredel, Fritz
    Kugelmass, I. Newton
    Kusuh (Judgement of the Orient)
    La Nauze, Charles D.
    Laird-Brown, May
    Lamb Tales from Shakespeare, illus. by A. Rackham
    Landrieux, Catherdral de Reins
    Lane, Rose Wilder
    Langstaff, J. Brett
    Lamier, Henry M.
    Lascelles, Amy (Yam) 1886-
    Lasker, Emmanuel
    Lathrop, Dorothy
    Lawrence, C.E. (God in the Thicket) Correspondence
  - Lasker - Leblanc (Box 45)
    Lasker, Dr. Emanuel 1933-1934
    Lasker, Dr. Emanuel 1928-1932
    Lawson, Agnes M.
    Le Roy, Eugene
    Lear, Edward
    Lear, John
    Leavelle, Charles Richard
    Le Blanc, Georgette Items
  - Le Blanc - Letter of Mozart (Box 45)
    Le Blanc, Georgette
    Lee, Charles Biog. & Photos
    Lee, Gerald Stanley Correspondence #1
    Lee, Gerald Stanley Correspondence #2
    Lee, Gerald Stanley Correspondence #3
    Lee, Harry
    Leeman, Jean
    Lethbridge, Alan
    A Letter to My Son (by a Soldier's Mother)
    Letters of Lord Byron Reviews
    Letters of Mozart Reviews
  - Letters of Richard Wayne - Libban (Box 45)
    Letters of Richard Wayne Reviews
    Letters and Second Diary of Samuel Pepys Reviews
    Letters Winnifred Correspondence Spice of Oxford
    Levens Bk. of Latin Letters
    Levy, Florence
    Lewis and Clarke Contest
    Lewisohn, Sam A.
    Ley, J.W.T.
    Liddon, Eloise Biog. & Photos
    Liddon, Eloise Reviews
  - Lieberman - Lockridge (Box 45)
    Lieberman, Frank
    Liefmann, Robert 1933 Reviews of "Cartels, Concerns & Trusts"
    Lillie, Amy Morris
    Lilly, Jean
    "Liliecronas Home"
    Limpus, Lowell M.
    Lindsay, Jack
    Lindsay, Samuel McCune Correspondence
    Link, Henry C.
    Literary Yearbook
    Littlefield, Walter
    Lloyd, Georgia
    Loch, J.M.
    Lockridge, Lt. Richard
  - Locke - Ludovici (Box 45)
    Locke, George H.
    Lods, Adolph
    Lombroso, Gina
    Lombroso, Gina Biog., Photos & Items
    Look (Eds.) FBI
    Loomis, Roger S.
    Lucas, Audrey Biog. & Photos
    Lucas, E.V.
    Lucas, E.V. Photos
    Lubbock, Basil
    Luckiesh, M.
    Ludendorff, Von Gerard Correspondence
    Ludovico, Anthony
  - Luffmann - McDermott (Box 45)
    Luffmann
    Lynch, Patricia Correspondence
    Mabie, Janet
    McAdoo, William
    Macartney, William
    Macbeth, J.H.C.
    McCabe, Joseph
    MacConnell, C.J.D.
    McCoy, John Pleasant
    McCrady, Marjorie Ellis & Wheele, Blanche
    McCulloch
  - McDermont - MacDonald (Box 45)
    McDermont, John Francis 1933-1934
    McDermont, John Francis 1928-1932
    MacDonald, Major Florence
    MacDonald, George
    MacDonald, Greville Correspondence
  - MacDonald - McLean (Box 45)
    MacDonald, Greville Biog. & Photos
    MacDonald, James
    MacFoll, Haldane
    McFerran, Doris
    Macfie, Ronald C.
    MacGregor, A.G. Biog., Photos & Items
    MacInnes, Tom
    McKay, Claude
    McKay, Clause Items
    McKenna, Robert W.
    MacKenzie, Colin
    MacKenzie, Compton Mr. Roosevelt
    MacKenzie, Compton
    Mackie, Ransom A.
    McKinney, Laurence
    MacSwiney, Terence Correspondence
    McLean, Margaret
  - McLean - McNeil (Box 45)
    McLean, Margaret 1928-1934
    Macmillan, Margaret
    MacNaughton, S.B.
    McNeil, Everett Correspondence
    McNeil, Everett Biog. & Items
  - McNeil (Box 45)
    McNeil, Everett
    McNeil, Everett Reviews
  - Maddox - Mahogany (Box 46)
    Maddox, Goynor
    Madariaga, S. de Correspondence
    Maeterlinck, Maurice Reviews
    Magnus, Laurie Correspondence
    Magie, Maurice
    Mahogany Association, Inc.
  - Maimonides - March (Box 46)
    Maimonides Guide for the Perplexed
    Major, H.D.A. et al
    Malamuth, Charles
    Malcoskey, Edna
    Malinowsky
    Mann, Heinrich
    Mann, Heinrich Correspondence & Items
    Manners, David J.
    Marbury, Elizabeth
    March, Nora Correspondence
  - March - Marot (Box 46)
    March, Phillips A.
    Marchant, Rev. James
    Marfield, Dwight
    Mme. Queena Mario 1933-1934
    Mario, Queena
    Marnas, M.
    Marot, Helen
  - Marriot - Mason (Box 46)
    Marriot, Charles
    Marriot, John A.R.
    Marryat, Captain
    Marsh, Helen
    Marshall, Bruce Correspondence
    Marshall, Bruce Biog., Photos & Items
    Marshall, Frank & MacBeth, J.C.H. Biog.
    Marhsall, Rachel
    Martel, (Capt.) Francis
    Martin, Bradley
    Martin, Edward
    Masefield, John Correspondence
    Massey, W.T.
    Massingham, H.J. Correspondence
    Masterman, Walter
    Mason, Lillian, A.N.
    Mason, J.W.T.
  - Mastermond - Mears (Box 46)
    (Untitled folder)
    Matthews, Dean W.R.
    Maurois, Andrea
    Mavor, James Correspondence
    Mavor, James Reviews
    Meacham, Lotta Allen Correspondence on "Belle Jones"
    Mears, Alice Monks
  - Mechling - Merrick (Box 46)
    Mechling, M.
    Meier, Frank
    Meiklejohn, Mrs. A.
    Melrose, Andrew
    Melville, Herman
    Manke, Frank G.
    Mercier, Cardinal
    Merezhkovsky, Dmitri
    Merrick, Leonard stories written by hand
    Merrick, Leonard #1 Correspondence (1906-1919)
  - Merrick I (Box 46)
    Merrick, Leonard #2 Correspondence (1920-1924)
    Merrick, Leonard #3 Correspondence (1925-1926)
    Merrick II
    Merrick, Leonard #4 Correspondence (1927-1929)
    Merrick, Leonard #5 Correspondence (1930-1936)
  - Merrick III (Box 46)
    Merrick, Leonard Reader's Reports
    Merrick, Leonard Articles & Special Columns
    Merrick, Leonard Articles & Features #2
    Merrick, Leonard Reviews
  - Merrick IV (Box 46)
  - Merrick V (Box 46)
    Merrick, Leonard Old Reviews
    Merrick, Leonard Literary Notes
    Merrick, Leonard Biog., Photos & Items
  - Merrick - Miller (Box 47)
    Merrick, Lesley Biog. & Photos
    Metzl, Ervine
    Meyer, Agnes E.
    Maynell, Viola
    Mickiewicz Correspondence
    Miller (Story Telling)
    Miller, Lt. Col. E.D.
    Miller, George T.
    Miller, Mrs. L.A. (Nellie)
  - Miller (Box 47)
    Miller, Leona (prize winner)
    Miller, Max Correspondence
    Miller, Max 1934
  - Milne, A. A.
    - Milne I (Box 47)
    - Milne II (Box 47)
    - Milne III (Box 47)
    - Milne IV (Box 47)
    - Milne V, Reader's Reports; Correspondence (Box 47)
    - Milne VI, Correspondence #2 (1926-1927); Reviews (Box 47)
    - Milne VII, #4 Correspondence (1932-1936) (Box 47)
    - Milne VIII, The Pocket Milne (Box 47)
  - Mitchell - Montague (Box 47)
    Mitchell, Lucy Sprogue Biog.
    Mitchell, Lucy Sprogue Correspondence
    Mitchell, Lucy Sprouge Reviews
    Mitchell, Brig. Gen. William Correspondence #1
    Mitchell, Brig. Gen. William Correspondence #2
    Mobhabghab, Faddoul
    Modes and Manners of the 19th Century Reviews
    Moncrieff
    Monkshood, G.F.
    Montague, Margaret Prescott Correspondence
  - Montaigne - Morman (Box 47)
    Montaigne
    Montgomery, Doris
    Montgomery
    Montizambert, Elizabeth
    de Montmorenci
    Moore, Cora
    Moore, Mrs. Evelyn Stuart
    Moore, Olive (insert): one folder "Virginia Moore 1928-1934" removed for return to E.P. Dutton September 3, 1974
    Morain, Alfred
    Moravia, Alberto - Mastrangelo - H
    Morgulis, Sergius
    Morley, Christopher Correspondence
    Morman, James
  - Morris - Morse (Box 47)
    Morris, Emanuel G.
    Morris, Robert T.
    Morrison
    Morisson, Robert 1928
    Morse, Elizabeth
  - Book: Kari the Elephant by Dhan Gopal Mukerji (Box 48)
  - Morse (Box 48)
    Morse, Elizabeth 1933 - 1934
    Morse, Elizabeth 1931 - 1932
    Morse, Elizabeth 1930
    Morse, Elizabeth 1929
    Morse, Elizabeth 1928
  - Morse - Moore (Box 48)
    Morse, Frank
    Morse, Katherine
    Moses, Montrose J. Correspondence & Items
    Moses, Montrose J.
    Moore, Virginia
  - Moss - Mukerii (Box 48)
    Moss, Geoffrey
    Mowrer, Paul Scott Biog. & Items
    Mowrer, Paul Scott Correspondence
    Mueller, Hans Alexander
  - Mukerji I (Box 48)
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1934
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1933
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1932
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1931
  - Mukerji II (Box 48)
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1930
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1930 cont.
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal Kennaday & Livingston
  - Mukerji III (Box 48)
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal Reviews
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1928
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1929
  - Mukerji IV (Box 48)
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal 1929 cont.
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal articles & personal items
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal Correspondence #1
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal reviews
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal reviews 2A
  - Mukerji V (Box 48)
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal Correspondence #2
  - Mukerji VI (Box 48)
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal photographs
    Mukerji, Dhan Gopal biological materials
  - Mullen - Munthe (Box 48)
    Mulgrave, Dorothy I & Manser, Rith B.
    Mullen, Pat (Man of Aran) Correspondence
    Mullen, Pat (Man of Aran) photos from movie
    Muller, Margarethe
    Muller, Dr. Richard Correspondence
    Muller, Prof. V.K.
    Munn, George F. (Mrs.)
    Munthe, Dr. Axel Correspondence #1
  - Munthe I (Box 48)
    Munthe, Dr. Axel Correspondence #2
  - Munthe II (Box 48)
    Munthe, Dr. Axel 1929 - 1932
    Munthe, Dr. Axel 1932 - 1934
    Munthe, Dr. Axel Articles & Personal Items
    Munthe, Dr. Axel Reviews - Illus. Ed.
  - Munthe - Murray (Box 49)
    Munthe, Dr. Axel Reviews
    Munthe, Dr. Axel Reviews 1930 –
    Murphy, Clyde
    Murphy, Lois Barelay
    Murray, John (at) Reviews
    Murry, John Middleton Correspondence
    Murry, John Middleton Items
    Murry, Ges. A.
  - My Dolly's Home - Nesbit (Box 49)
    My Dolly's Home
    Myers, John Myers
    Nablo, James Benson
    Nahoum, Jules
    Narischkin, Princess
    Neilson, Frances Fullerton Correspondence
    Nesbit, (Mrs. E) (1901, 1903 - ?)
    Nesbit, William
  - Neumann - New Testament (Box 49)
    Neumann, Robert
    Nevinson, Henry (Voice of Freedom)
    New Testament in Basic English
  - Newbold - Nightshade (Box 49)
    Newbold, Walton
    Newbolt, Henry Correspondence
    Newton, Mrs. Alma
    Nicholl, Louise Townsend
    Nichols, Adelaide
    Nichols, Norah
    Nichols, Robert Correspondence
    Nicholson, Norman Fine Review
    Nicolai Biology of War
    Nightshade
  - Nims - Norris (Box 49)
    Nims, William Clement
    Niven, Frederick
    Noel, E. Percy
    Norris, Charles G. Correspondence #3
    Norris, Charles G. Correspondence #4
  - Norris I (Box 49)
    Norris, Charles G. 1930
    Norris, Charles G. 1929
    Norris, Charles G. 1928
    Norris, Charles G. Curtis Brown, Ltd.
    Norris, Charles G. Articles & Items
  - Norris II (Box 49)
    Norris, Charles G. Reviews
  - Norris III (Box 49)
    Norris, Charles G. Biog., Photos, Items
  - Norris IV (Box 49)
    Norris, Charles G. Correspondence #2
    Norris, Herbert
  - Obata - Older (Box 49)
    Obata, Shiggosha Correspondence
    Obata, translator of Pe Le, Works of Reviews
    Obermeyer, Rosemary
    Odell, Joseph H. Biog. & Photos
    Odell, Joseph H. Correspondence
    Ohanian, Arnim
    Old Bristol Potteries
    Older, Mrs. Fremont
  - Oliver - Ortmann (Box 49)
    Oliver, Dr. Wade
    Olsen, James P.
    Oman, Carola
    Oman, Sir Charles
    Oman, Khayan Illus. By Fish
    Orchard, W.E.
    Ormsbee, David Biog., Photos, & Items
    Ortmann, Otto
  - Ossendowski (Box 49)
    Ossendowski, Dr. Ferdinand Correspondence
  - Ossendowski - Otis (Box 50)
    Ossendowski, Ferdinand Biog., Photos & Items
    Ossendowski, Ferdinand Reviews
    Osty, Eugene
    O'Sullivan, Vincent
    Otis, James
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 50)
    Overseas Press Club
    Overseas Press Club of America
  - Owen - Parkhurst (Box 50)
    Owen, John
    Packard, Vance
    Paisley, E.W. Reviews
    Park, Dr. William H.
    Packhurst, Helen Correspondence
  - Parsons - Patrick (Box 50)
    Parsons, Alice Beal
    "Paston, George"
    Patri, Angelo
    Patrick, Diana Correspondence
    Patrick, Diana 1935
  - Patrick - Pearson (Box 50)
    Patrick, Diana 1933-1934
    Patrick, Diana 1928-1932
    Patrick, Diana Watt
    Patrick, Diana Biog., Photos, & Items
    Paul, H.M. Literary Ethics
    Payne, Barrie
    Pearson, Adeline
  - Peattie - Peyser (Box 50)
    Peattie, Louise Redfield
    Peck, Annie S. Correspondence
    Penny, Mrs.
    Pentamerone, The
    Pepys, Samuel (Howarth, R.G. ed.)
    Perry, Ralph Barton Correspondence
    Pershing, General John G. Correspondence
    Pertwee, Ernest
    Peterson, Anna J.
    Petulengro, Gypsy
    Peyser, Ethel R.
    Peyser, Ethel R. Brandt & Brandt
  - Phelps I (Box 50)
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1934
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1933
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1932
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1931
  - Phelps II (Box 50)
    Phelps, Prof. W. Lyon 1930